麦克斯  这些是什么鬼
Max, what is all this?
我还以为上次你骂我乱买双层厕纸后
I thought we were running fancy purchases past each other
我们买奢侈品都得互相监督呢
since you yelled at me for splurging on two-ply.
何不直接用一元纸钞擦您的皇家屁股呢
You might as well wipe with dollar bills, your royal heinie.
这是我为戒暴食匿名会的订单
This is for a big cake order I got
买的材料啦
from Over-Eaters Anonymous.
这订单就像他们的成员一样  老"大"了
And, like it's members, it's a big 'un.
我还以为我们现在不接这种特殊订单了
I thought we didn't take special orders anymore
因为我们开了甜品酒吧
since we opened the dessert bar.
就像是女孩们得到戒指后
You know, like how girls stop doing mouth stuff
就不干"口活儿"了
after they get a ring.
这就是为什么我不给女人们戒指
Which is why I don't give girls rings.
他们想要集体偷吃一天  我想帮忙嘛
They're having a group cheat day and I wanna help them.
这是我回"报复"社会的方式
It's my way of giving nothing.
麦克斯  这样太坏了
Max, that's terrible.
我们不能纵容那些真有毛病的人
We can't enable people that have a real problem.
他们会给我们一千块
They're paying us 1,000 bucks.
诚如我所说  顾客永远是上帝
Like I said, the customer is always right.
有了这笔巨款
You know, with that kind of money,
咱们能从双层厕纸提升到湿纸巾呢
we could go from two-ply to wet wipes.
土豪  你双层厕纸的巨轮能缓缓吗
Pfft, slow your two-ply roll, money bags.
我们小店那半边都没空位
Ugh, there's no room on our side.
阿憨这倒挺空
Han's side is empty though.
就像侏儒真人秀的观赏派对一样空
Just like his Little People, Big World viewing parties.
我去看过一次呢
I went once.
阿憨又留了条信息
Oh, Han left another note
说不许我们把东西放他的东西上
telling us not to put our stuff on his stuff.
喝掉全球的酒也无法让我愿意把
There's not enough alcohol in the world
我的"东西"放他的"东西"上
to get my stuff on his stuff.
"亲爱的姑娘们  你们好吗
"Dear girls, how are you?
最近热得仿佛不像冬天  对吧"
Been unseasonably hot lately, hasn't it?"
真是会棒打树丛  不着边际兜圈子
He really beats around the bush.
世上的酒还是不够让他"棒"打我"树丛"
Again, not enough alcohol.
"十分希望你们
"I'd really appreciate
可以把自己的存货放在自己那..."
if you kept your supplies on your--"
他的留言比你的
Wow, his notes are more boring
"还记得我有钱的那会儿"故事还无聊啊
than your "Remember when I had money" stories.
别这样  麦克斯  咱们是在吐槽阿憨
Come on, Max. We're slamming Han.
别跑题了
Let's stay focused.
但还记得我有钱的那会儿吗
Remember when I had money, though?
我正在动手给阿憨回应呢
I'm crafting my response to Han right now.
"火"气不用太大
I wanna keep it light.
我跟你说过
Did I ever tell you
当年我家真有储钱间吗
we actually had a money room
-跟人家漫画里一样  -说过了
- like in Richie Rich comics? - Yep.
你们好啊  姑娘们
Hello, girls.
最近有读到什么好文字吗
Read anything good lately?
比如一张写在便条上  署名有
Perhaps a note on stationary that says,
"某软心糖豆爱好者敬上"的纸张
"From the desk of a jelly bean addict?
阿憨  如果你有话要对我们说
Han, if you have something to say,
请你直视我们的膝盖  大大方方地说
look us in the kneecaps and say it.
我闻到了烟味  每次一有烟
I smell smoke, and where there's smoke,
几乎都是我的东西被烧了
there's usually something of mine burning.
厄尔  帮我看着店
Earl, watch the diner for me.
没问题
Sure thing.
姑娘们  帮我看着店
Girls, watch the diner for me.
我又得去上厕所了
I gotta go to the bathroom again.
我的前列腺变化速度比《观点》换主持人还快
My prostate changes faster than the lineup of The View.
-卡洛琳  帮我看着店  -麦克斯  帮我看着店
- Caroline, watch the diner for me. - Max, watch the diner for me.
厄运结  你欠我一瓶饮料
Jinx, you owe me a soda.
但不要店里的饮料
But not from here.
好笑吧
Hilar, right?
不是你好笑
Not you.
是兰迪在给我视频蹭大胸[摩托艇]呢
Randy was giving me a Facetime motorboat.
卡洛琳你好啊
Hey, Caroline.
海水海风有些刺骨啊
Arr, it was a bit nippy in there.
哟呵  船长你好
Ahoy, Captain.
我为什么要配合这个烂哏
Oh, why am I playing along?
我们不能再视频做爱下去了
Well, we should probably stop having phone sex
我在粉红莓酸奶店
'cause I'm at Pinkberry
得做好多决定呢  比如挑什么配料
and I got a lot of decisions to make.
有空聊  免得你裤裆里粉红莓
Well, call me back so your pinkberries
憋坏憋成铁青蓝莓
don't become blueberries.
姑娘们  自重  这里可是工作场所
Girls, come on. This is a workplace.
你们觉得我能用洗碗精洗这玩意吗
Do you think I can use dish soap on these?
你应该用汽油点了它们
You should use gasoline on those.
所以...
So...
你跟兰迪是不是到了
isn't it about time you and Randy
应该正式宣布复合的时候了
made your relationship official again?
你跟他说话比跟我说话还多
You talk to him more than you talk to me,
这导致了我要说的第二点
which brings me to my second point:
我好受伤
I'm hurt.
我跟他才没有在谈恋爱
We are not in a relationship.
也没有远距离恋爱
Or a long-distance relationship.
我们只是两个在寻觅完美灯光
We are just two people looking for good lighting
照耀我们性器官的狼友
for our sex parts.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我想找厄尔·华盛顿
I'm looking for Earl Washington.
你怎么知道厄尔的姓氏
How do you know Earl's last name?
他就连驾照上都只有厄尔呢
Even his license just says Earl.
你不是直播卫星电视台的人吧
You're not the DirecTV lady, are you?
他说你们的付费电视频道
'Cause he told us he's not paying for Starz
得来点"有料"的内容  他才会付钱
till the channel actually gets some.
厄尔·华盛顿  大概1米88
Earl Washington, about 6'2",
壮得像条牛  头顶浓密爆炸头
strong as an ox, big bushy afro?
亲爱的  我们把厄尔缩小了
Honey, we shrunk the Earl.
你上次见到这位"大厄尔"是什么时候
Um, when was the last time you saw this "Big Earl"?
1961年  我们是爱人
1961. We were sweethearts.
但我回古巴哈瓦那看家人
But I went to Havana to visit my family
顺便想给厄尔带几根古巴雪茄
and to bring Earl back some cigars.
结果我们那里爆发革命  就只剩下共产主义了
Then the revolution came and the rest is communism.
有人跨越时间空间千里寻厄尔
Earl's got people hunting him down across time and space,
而我连第二次约会都要不到
and I can't get a second date?
厄尔
Earl!
果然是你
Oh, it's you.
我认出了你那范儿
I recognize that swagger.
她从哪能看出范儿
She does?
皮拉尔
Wow, Pilar.
我的雪茄带来了吗
You have my cigars?
他能记得她  可昨天
He remembers her, but yesterday
他还因为记错  在快餐店干了一整天呢
he accidentally worked a full shift at Denny's.
真不敢相信我能在你面前
I can't believe I'm here.
1984年的时候  我试着用移动厕所漂来
You know, I tried to float to you on a porta-potty in 1984,
但这方法大失败
but it did not work out.
我上次这么兴奋至极
I haven't been this excited
还是我发现原来我不在快餐店打工的时候呢
since I found out I didn't work at Denny's.
厄尔  依旧还是人中之龙
You are still a fine piece of man, Earl.
而你依旧美  到  爆
And you are beau-ti-ful.
美人  咱们走吧
Girl, let's get outta here.
你对完全享有在"上面"的权利意愿如何
How do you feel about exclusively being on top?
他宝刀未老
He's still got it.
他的宝刀平常都藏哪了
Where is he hiding it?
太萌太有爱了
That is so cute.
希望她知道怎么做心肺复苏术
I hope she knows CPR.
那帮暴食客的银子花得可真值回票价
Those over-eaters are really getting their money's worth.
尤其你还往蛋糕里加了一层肉
Especially since you added the meat layer.
跟土豆搭配相得益彰
It's gonna compliment the potatoes.
说到相得奶涨
Speaking of complimenting my potatoes,
你听听兰迪给我的短信
listen to what Randy texted.
不用了  谢谢  我要喜欢黄书
No, thanks. If I liked porn,
我就不会扔掉苏菲跟奥列格的
I wouldn't have thrown away Sophie and Oleg's
"弄瓦之喜"卡片了
"We're Having a Baby" card.
不  这短信异常不带任何色情
No, this is disturbingly clean.
"明天会在纽约纽瓦克机场停留一小时
"Have an hour layover in Newark Airport tomorrow.
但却感觉与你咫尺天涯"
So close and yet so far."
他这话什么意思
What does that mean?
他是想看我的奶子还是下面
Does he wanna see my boobs or my junk?
他说的是我的语言
Now he's speaking my language.
浪漫喜剧语
The language of romantic comedy.
他想要更多
He wants more.
要看我的屁股吗
My butt?
麦克斯  他想跟你在机场见面
Max, he wants you to meet him at the airport.
机场是所有伟大爱情故事浪漫的高潮
Airports are the romantic climax to every great love story.
《卡萨布兰卡》
Casablanca,
《真爱至上》
Love Actually,
《航班蛇患》
Snakes on a Plane.
现在我懂了
Ah, now I get it.
你就指他想看我身上哪里吧
So point to it on my body.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我在试着逗我宝宝笑
I'm trying to make the baby laugh.
比如这个笑话
Here's one...
两个姑娘走进一家甜品酒吧
Two girls walk into a dessert bar
就卡在里面一辈子了
and they never leave.
你们看  毫无反应
Ah, see? Nothing.
你们俩觉得我很有趣  对吧
You girls think I'm funny. Right?
你嫁给了奥列格  肯定很有幽默感啦
You married Oleg, so you have a sense of humor.
没懂
I don't get it.
我试着让芭芭拉笑
I'm trying to make Barbara laugh,
但就像杰·雷诺10点的节目一样
but you know what? I'm like Leno at 10:00.
观众毫无反应
You know? I'm getting nothing.
你们看  静悄悄
See? Crickets.
你试过"我偷走你鼻子啦"这招吗
Have you tried any got-your-nose material?
每次都能逗卡洛琳笑
Always makes Caroline laugh.
别这样
Stop!
快把我鼻子还我
Give me back my nose!
这个真的不好笑
You know what? That's really not funny.
大家都说
You know what they say.
像她这么大的婴儿应该要会笑了
That babies that are this age are supposed to laugh,
所以她不笑我很担心
and that gets me really worried.
万一芭芭拉不知道什么好笑怎么办
'Cause what if Barbara has no idea what's funny?
就像网飞的喜剧一样
Like a Netflix comedy.
《毒枭》就挺好笑啊
Narcos is pretty funny,
不过可能你得亲身经历才会觉得好笑
but I guess you had to be there.
等等  我有一个
Wait a minute. I got something.
她连放屁笑话都不喜欢
Ah, she doesn't even like fart jokes.
我们也不喜欢
Neither do we.
别随便代表我发言
Speak for yourself.
好了
All right.
你回兰迪短信了吗
Did you text Randy back?
我不知道怎么回他
I don't know what to say to him.
你觉得回"新手机  这是谁"怎么样
How does, "New phone, who dis?" sound?
如果你是莎莉  你一定不会遇到哈利
If you were Sally, you would have never met Harry.
如果他想要我去机场见他
If he wants me to meet him at the airport,
那他就得直接点问我
he's gonna have to come out and ask me.
他想你去找他啊
He wants you to meet him.
他只是用浪漫的语言来表达而已
He's just speaking in the language of romance.
而你不听懂他的话
Which you don't understand
因为这话中没带有恶搞的打嗝声
'cause it doesn't have any burps in it.
比如你把我当初对你说的"你好"
You thought when I first said "Hi" to you
误解为邀请你搬来跟我同住六年
it meant I wanted you to move in with me for six years.
你对我问好时  已掳获我心  是我的错
Sorry if you had me at "Hello".
18小时的苦工后  宝贝完工
There she is 18 hours later.
老娘此生最大的成就
Mama's greatest accomplishment:
枫糖香草朗姆蛋糕
Maple vanilla rum cake
内含覆盆子奶油奶酪夹心
with a raspberry cream cheese filling
与白巧克力碎
and a white chocolate crumble.
另外  里面还有火腿
Also, there's a ham in it.
人能光凭看着某样东西
Can you have a contact heart attack
就得到心脏病吗
from looking at something?
我的左臂现在有点酸麻感
'Cause my left arm is tingly.
把这个"大家伙塞进后面"吧
Let's load this monster in the back.
这句话我不知道说过多少次了
How many times have I said that?
我能吃一片那个火腿吗
Ooh, can I get a hunk of that ham?
不许
No!
我们那边没位置放了
Oh, there's no room on our side.
天啊  麦克斯  这怎么那么重
Oh, my God, Max, why is this so heavy?
罪魁祸首肯定是里面那层热狗
That's gonna be the layer of hot dogs.
就放阿憨那半边吧
Let's just put it on Han's side.
先把纸条移开  我等会再烧了
Move his note. I'll burn it later.
这张还是公证过的呢
Aw, he got this one notarized.
他还是一名公证员
And he's a notary.
他这人有许多面
There's a lot of sides to that square.
所以呢
So...
我一直在想你去机场穿什么
I've been thinking about your airport outfit.
你可能会不喜欢  但我觉得是时候
You're not gonna like this, but I think it may be time
你买第三件衬衫了
for you got a third shirt.
你应该也不喜欢这句话
You're not gonna like this.
但我觉得是时候你去结识第二个朋友了
I think it's time for you to get a second friend.
你都六个月没见到兰迪了
You haven't seen Randy in six months.
虽然你在手机上见过兰迪的部分"身体"
I mean, you've seen parts of him on your phone,
但你都没见到完整的他
but you haven't seen the whole.
我有见到他菊花[完整]啊
Oh, I've seen the hole.
他出浴的时候滑倒了
He fell getting out of the shower.
你是闹哪样啊
What is wrong with you?
我知道你明明就很爱他
I know you're crazy about him.
是啊  可是万一他不想我去怎么办
I am, but what if he doesn't want me to come?
万一我到了现场  跟他说"嘿嘿"
What if I get there and I'm like, "Hey,"
结果他说... "那啥..."
and he's like, "Uh, hey..."
我不想难为情啊
I don't wanna be embarrassed.
那就请你这辈子都别这么说"嘿"
Then don't say "Hey" like that ever.
而且你什么时候开始介意难为情这种事了
And since when do you care about being embarrassed?
你的雨衣是个垃圾袋
Your raincoat is a trash bag.
它跟我的胶带鞋子很配啊
Ugh, it matches my duct tape shoes.
我才不要去机场
I am not going to the airport.
没问题  皮拉尔
Uh, sure, Pilar.
就像大金刚游戏一样  "杠杠"地
It's on like Donkey Kong.
跟皮拉尔怎么样啦
How's it going with Pilar?
你们俩疯狂的孩子玩得开心吗
You crazy kids still having fun?
她快把我累垮了
She's wearing me out.
至少你有个人啊
Well, at least you have somebody.
冷静啊  寂寞孤岛[乐队名]
Whoa, simmer down, Lonely Island.
厄尔  怎么回事
Earl, what's going on?
她想看她这五十年来
She wants to see everything she's missed
错过的一切
in the last 50 years.
现在她还要去迪士尼乐园
Now she wants to go to Disney World.
厄尔  你需要喘口气
You know what, Earl? You need to breathe.
要不我们一起做你腿部血液不循环时
How about we go for one of those invigorating walks we take
都会做的健走吧
whenever your leg blood isn't moving?
需要你的拐杖[走路]吗  厄尔
Do you need your Walker, Earl?
当然啦
Of course I do.
谢谢
Thank you.
就直接放在...
Just put it right over--
无可否认这蛋糕看上去很赞
That admittedly gorgeous cake
但它不是威廉斯堡餐厅的所有物
is not the property of the Williamsburg Diner.
我没兴趣继续抱着这玩意
I'm losing interest real fast here Han.
我该放哪儿
Where am I putting this box?
我去把蛋糕搬走
I'm moving the cake.
人若犯憨  憨必犯人
You play with the bull, you get the Han.
看来我的混合健身课今天又让我失望了
I guess CrossFit failed me again today.
你就去了一次  还晕了过去
You went once and you passed out.
那是因为缺水
I didn't hydrate.
瓜娃子
Oh, boy.
天啊
Oh, my God.
那是一根热狗吗
Is that a hot dog?
快醒醒  阿憨  快醒醒
Wake up, Han. Wake up.
你只是在做一个很可怕的梦
You're having a terrible dream
梦见自己毁掉了那俩恶女很重要的东西
where you destroyed something very important to the girls
她们绝对会弄死你的
and they're going to kill you.
是的  我们还在案发现场
Yeah, we're still here.
你把蛋糕弄掉了  这事真发生了
You dropped the cake. This is happening.
我都干了什么
What have I done?
看来有人就"酱"自己作"贱"自缚
Looks like someone got themselves in a little jam.
覆盆子果酱
Mmm, raspberry.
别舔了
Stop licking things.
我们得把蛋糕恢复原样
We need to put this back together.
就这样  可以复原
Yes, yes, this is working.
没人会发现的
No one will be the wiser.
我们只需在外表上一层糖霜
We'll just frost over the crime.
怎么还会有火腿
Why is there a ham?
这蛋糕太莫名其妙了
This cake makes no sense!
给我起来
Get up.
你真是丢人现眼
You're making a fool of yourself.
连我这个早些时候
And that's coming from a guy
被烘手机烫到蛋蛋的人都觉得你丢人
who burnt his nuts on a hand dryer earlier.
那你告诉我该怎么办
Tell me what to do.
淡定
Relax.
这个蛋糕没有家人
This cake had no family,
没有朋友  也没有牙科记录
no friends, no dental records.
这种事我有经验
I've done this before.
当然我说的是处理别的"蛋糕"
With other cakes, of course.
人家好怕怕
I'm so scared.
皮拉尔真的让厄尔处于两难的地步
Earl is really in a bad way over Pilar.
我从来没看见他如此困惑
I've never seen him that confused.
那你肯定没见过他系衣服扣子的时候
Well, then you've never watched him button a shirt.
-蛋糕在哪儿  -蛋糕吗
- Where's the cake? - The cake?
我们明明就放在这儿啊
We put it right here.
它不可能长出小脚  然后自己跑掉
It couldn't have grown little legs and walked away.
小脚
Little legs?
阿憨
Han!
奥列格  你有见过我们的蛋糕吗
Oleg, have you seen our cake?
我见过很多蛋糕
I see a lot of cakes.
这里是纽约城  蛋糕多得要死
This is New York City. Cakes up the wazoo.
薄饼"蛋糕"  小宝贝"蛋糕"  拍手"蛋糕"
Pancakes, baby cakes, patty cakes.
其实真应该改名叫纽蛋城
They should change the name to New Cake City.
他肯定知道什么
He knows something.
虽然不多  但多少知道一些
Not much, but something.
但这名字还真挺适合纽约的
But that is a pretty great name for New York.
厄尔  你有看见蛋糕大小的人
Earl, have you seen a man-sized cake
抬着一个人形大小的蛋糕吗
being carried by a cake-sized man?
我有自己的事要烦
I have other stuff on my mind.
我得告诉皮拉尔我不想去迪士尼乐园
I gotta tell Pilar I don't wanna go to Disney World
火人节我也不想去了
and Burning Man's off too.
姑娘们
Hello, girls.
我在想工作餐要不要给你们加个鸡腿
I've been thinking of adding a chicken leg to the shift meal.
意下如何啊
Thoughts?
你把我们的蛋糕藏哪儿了
Where'd you hide our cake?
跟你身体其余部分藏在一起吗
With the rest of your body?
你的咖啡被人拉屎了吗  这么炸毛
Who crapped in your coffee?
首先我要说
First I'm gonna say:
强烈赞成工作餐加鸡腿
That's a strong yes on the chicken leg.
现在快说我的枫糖香草夹热狗蛋糕去哪儿了
Now, where's my maple vanilla cake with hot dog filling?
我们放在你那半边的台子上  现在不见了
We put it on your side of the shelf and now it's gone.
我完全不知道你们在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
抱歉失陪了  我要去"蛋"个电话
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have to cake a phone call.
我是说  打个电"糕"
I mean, make a phone cake.
搜他身  麦克斯
Search him, Max.
连他的卡通小内裤都要搜
All the way down to his Underoos.
来搜我的小裤裤啊
Check my Underoos.
里面兜着美味可口的东西
There's something sweet in there,
但肯定不是蛋糕
but it's not cake.
你们没有证据
You've got nothing on me.
奥列格  告诉她们我没见过她们的蛋糕
Oleg, tell them I haven't seen their cake.
对吧  好兄弟
Right, bro?
蛋糕  什么蛋糕  我见过很多蛋糕
Cake? What cake? I see a lot of cakes.
这里是纽约城  蛋糕多得要死
This is New York City. Cakes up the wazoo.
薄饼"蛋糕"  小宝贝"蛋糕"  拍手"蛋糕"
patty cakes, pancakes, baby cake.
-其实真应该改名叫... -纽蛋城
- They should name the city, uh-- - New Cake City.
我们知道了
Yeah, we got it.
或许阿憨说的是实话
Maybe Han's telling the truth.
你觉得有没有可能其中一名暴食客
Do you think one of those over-eaters
趁我们不注意偷偷溜进来吃掉了
could have snuck in here without us knowing?
你也看到后面地方有多狭窄
You saw how cramped it is back there.
今天早上我想进来还得先进左奶再进右奶
This morning I had to go in one boob at a time.
那能去哪儿呢
Where could it be?
钥匙丢在里面过一次而已  需要这样吗
Just 'cause your keys were in there one time.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我们来啦
We're here.
没错  我和冰山妹
Yeah, me and the ice queen.
如果她还不会笑
You know, if she doesn't laugh soon,
人们就要以为她是德国人了
people are gonna think she's German.
她可以用那台巨型婴儿车
She's getting real monster truck rally
参加疯狂大脚赛车了
with that carriage.
看来我只能再做一个蛋糕了
Well, I guess I'm gonna have to make another cake.
我手机收到了60则"随口问问"的语音留言
I have 60 "Just checking in" voicemails on my phone
都在问问问
asking about it.
61则了
Oh, 61.
可你得去机场见兰迪啊
But you have to go meet Randy at the airport.
我才不去机场
I'm not going to the airport.
再说了  我在机场便利店有太多仇家
Besides, I have too many enemies at Hudson News.
这是我吃过第二好吃的热狗蛋糕
This is the second best hot dog cake I've ever had.
我不想急着下结论
I don't want to jump to conclusions,
但我觉得那是我们的热狗蛋糕
but I think that's our hot dog cake.
苏菲  这蛋糕哪来的
Sophie, where did you get that?
奥列格给的
Oleg.
想不到他会把这玩意埋蛋糕里吧
Can you believe he buried this?
幸好我善于发掘
Good thing that I can dig.
是阿憨干的  如果能让你们好过点
It was Han. If it makes you feel any better,
我们把蛋糕铲进桶里时  他一直在哭
he cried as we shoveled it into a bucket.
阿憨
Han!
快滚出来
Get out here!
我们知道你毁了我们的蛋糕
We know you killed our cake.
你居然出卖我
You sold me out?
把我的48块5还给我  你个告密者
I want my 48.50 back, you stool pigeon.
我做不到埋个蛋糕
I can't bury a cake
却不拿一点回家给我老婆吃
and not bring some home for my wife.
我的结婚誓词你是知道的啊
You heard my vows.
这都是你们的错
This is your fault
谁让你们不看我的留言
for not paying attention to my notes.
准备去见上帝[制造者]吧  阿憨
Prepare to meet your maker, Han.
我猜你的制造者应该是芭比娃娃制造商
Which I'm assuming is Mattel.
求你们放我一条生路
Please don't kill me.
我上有...下有...
I have so much... A lot...
反正就是有值得活下去的理由啦
well, some things to live for.
你们听见了吗
Did you hear that?
她们俩吓唬阿憨
Ah, the girls scared Han,
让芭芭拉发笑了
and it made Barbara laugh.
我猜她喜欢听到别的宝宝倒霉
Ah, I guess she likes to hear other babies in danger.
果然是我的女儿
That's my girl.
厄尔
Hi, Earl.
我好高兴能坐飞机去佛罗里达  而不是抱着
I am excited to fly to Florida instead of floating there
雪佛兰老爷车的门漂过去
on the door of a '57 Chevy.
厄尔  你有什么话想跟皮拉尔说吗
Earl, is there anything you wanna tell Pilar
关于你们的迪士尼之旅的事
about your trip to Disney World?
有  我...
Yeah, I, uh...
买了公园套票
got the park hopper.
花三个公园的钱  却只能进两个公园
It's two parks for the price of three.
厄尔
Earl?
死就死吧
Oh, hell.
皮拉尔
Uh, Pilar...
我不想去迪士尼乐园
I don't wanna got Disney World.
我甚至不喜欢《狮子王》
I didn't even like The Lion King.
非洲元素太多了
Too much Africa stuff.
我真的不知道该怎么消化
I honestly don't know how to process
居然有人不喜欢《狮子王》这件事
somebody not liking The Lion King.
听着  皮拉尔  该喝的酒我全喝了
Look, Pilar, I've drank it all,
该抽的我也全抽了  该干的事也全干了
I've smoked it all, I've done it all.
而你才开始你的旅程
You are just starting out on your ride.
我不想拖慢你的脚步
I don't wanna slow you down.
我明白
I see.
这就是为什么我不想去机场
This is why I'm not going to the airport.
她现在肯定觉得难为情
She's probably so embarrassed right now.
你觉得我肯定会难为情
You'd think I'd be embarrassed
因为我大老远跑来找你  你却拒绝我
because I came all this way here for you,
但我不后悔
but I don't regret it.
不好意思
Uh, excuse me?
能给我上点黄芥末配蛋糕吃吗
Can I get some mustard for this cake?
厄尔  如果我不来找你
Earl, if I didn't come,
我就会一直想  我们之间的各种可能性
I'd always have wondered what could have been.
我很开心你能来
I am glad you came.
让我知道  我这颗心脏承受力很强
Showed me my heart can take a lot.
不管之前这颗心脏的主人是谁
Whoever had this one before me
那人一个定是个慢跑者
must have been a jogger.
很高兴见到你  厄尔
It was great seeing you, Earl.
我要去振翅"高飞"了
Now, I'm gonna go get my Goofy on.
皮拉尔
Uh, Pilar,
我能搭你的便车去机场吗
can I catch a ride with you to the airport?
我要去找个男人
I gotta meet a guy.
对啊  我猜我也该去找个男人了
Yeah, I guess I gotta meet a guy too.
卡洛琳
Caroline...
你要一起吗
do you wanna come?
我还以为你不会叫上我呢
I thought you'd never ask.
那我们是同搭一辆车吗
So, should we share a cab?
在古巴  我曾跟一匹马同住一间公寓
You know, in Cuba, I shared an apartment with a horse.
那也太"怪"了吧
Well, that's just weird.
再见  厄尔
Bye, Earl.
他睡着了
Aw, he's asleep.
没错  他是睡着了
Yep, he's asleep.
卡洛琳  快点
Caroline, hurry up.
我们要赶不上了
Now we're gonna be late.
那里明明有很多人
Ugh, there were plenty of people
可以扶那个人坐回他的轮椅
who could have helped that guy back into his wheelchair.
好啦  兰迪上一班飞机在第四航站楼降落
All right, Randy's last flight landed at terminal four,
他下一班飞机在第六航站楼
and his next flight is out of terminal six.
他应该随时会到这里
He should be here any second.
你看起来真美
You look beautiful.
是咩
You sure?
我牙齿上有东西吗
Do I have anything in my teeth?
只有你拿来当臼齿的玉米糖
Just the candy corn you use as a molar.
他在那儿
There he is!
兰迪
Randy!
抱歉  我不确定我有生之年会不会
Sorry, I'm not sure I'll ever get to have
有自己的机场时刻
my own airport moment.
卡洛琳  你在这里干什么
Caroline, what're you doing here?
麦克斯
Max!
先生  我需要你直勾勾地看着我的眼睛
Sir, I'm gonna need you to look deep into my eyes
因为我要搜你身了
while I frisk you.
麻烦你先把上衣脱了
And I'm gonna need you to take off that shirt.
这要求对我来说是家常便饭
This actually kind of happens to me a lot.
甚至进图书馆也要脱
Even in libraries.
我的上衣也要脱吗
Should I take my shirt off too?
不必  你是在机场  不是在麦当劳打野战
No, you're in an airport, not a McDonald's.
麦克斯
Max, I--
我想不到你真的会来见我
I didn't think you were actually coming to see me.
因为你也没有真的问我啊
Well, 'cause you didn't actually ask.
你看起来真不错
You look great.
奶头敏感  麻烦轻点好吗
Easy on the nipples there, Sheryl.
好了  你可以通过了
All right, you're good.
虽然没必要把上衣穿上
No need to put your shirt back on, though.
你不用脱
You're good.
你能来我真的很开心
I'm really happy you came.
真的吗
You are?
那你为什么不直接找我来
Then why didn't you just ask me?
可能我担心你会拒绝
I guess I was worried you'd say no,
然后我会难为情吧
and I'd be embarrassed.
我还担心你不想我来
I was worried you didn't want me to come
然后我来了  我会难为情呢
and then I'd be embarrassed.
经典的浪漫误会
Classic misunderstanding.
我知道我们不该再爱上对方  可...
Look, I-I know we're not supposed to get attached, but...
大胆说出来
Say it.
我想更近一步
I want something more.
我想跟你交往
I want a relationship.
大胆回应他
Say it back.
我没意见
I wouldn't hate that.
差不多了
Close enough.
做戏要做全套吗
So we're doing this?
因为如果不做  我就得回到安检员的怀抱
Because if not, I gotta get back to Sheryl.
我的鞋还在她那儿呢
She still has my shoes.
来吧  不做不行啊
Uh, yeah, I think we have to.
卡洛琳就指着看这一幕了
I mean, this is all Caroline has.
这一幕太美了
Oh, it's so beautiful.
拜托  冷漠的人们
Oh, come on, people.
你们也听到了  满足一下我的意淫啊
You heard her. This is all I have.